

Payam Zahedi

MOBILE DEVELOPER

Mobile Developer with robust soft skills and proven experience in mobile application development in a test-driven environment with more than 8 years of experience (3 years in flutter). I've started with Android Java and learned Kotlin and Flutter along the way. As Flutter Developer, I've worked for about 4 companies and developed more than 8 applications in different industries so far. I am also very interested in open source and was able to work and publish more than 10 open source projects. Furthermore, I have the ability to adapt myself to different work cultures and the ability to work within a tight deadline.

pzahedi1995@gmail.com 📞 +98- 939 - 066 - 2636 💿 Iran

payam-zahedi

in payamzahedi95

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Sep 2022 - Present Senior Flutter Developer, Snapp Mobile, Germany Remote • Jul 2021 - Sep 2022 Senior Software Engineer, REKAB Technologies, Turkey Remote

• Jun 2020 - Jul 2021 Senior Flutter Developer, Ra Secret Project, Remote Mobile Developer, Dropp Technologies Group, Iran Jun 2019 - May 2020

• Jan 2016 - Dec 2018 Android Developer, Targeting, Iran

OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

- Dart Persian tools: An anthology of a variety of tools for the Persian language which you can use in all platform that dart supports
- Fantom: Open API generator for Dart & Flutter. Written with Pure Dart
- Flutter Breadcrumb: Flutter Widget that can easily create Breadcrumb in Flutter.
- Flutter Iconly: The Flutter implementation of Iconly icon sets.
- More Open source Projects

SKILLS

• Flutter: Expert

• Android: Expert

• Java: Advanced

• Kotlin: Good

• Swift: Good

Python: Good

Bloc, Riverpod, Provider,

• Mvvm, Mvp, Clean

• Http, Dio, Socket

GetIt

Hive, get_storage, Sqfentity

application security

 Coroutines, Coil, Jetpack compose

• CI/CD: Azure, Code magic, GitHub actions

· GitHub, GitLab

• Trello, Notion, Jira, Taiga

Teamwork

problem-solving

· Active learning

WORK EXPERIENCE IN DETAIL



Senior Developer Remote, Germany | Sep 2022 - Present

<u>Snapp Mobile</u> is part of the Snapp companies, a stable parent company with a long history of successful project deliveries and access to nearly 150 designers and developers for project scalability and expertise.

- Struct Clean Architecture based on **Riverpod** and **Freezed** in flutter.
- Worked on multiplatform app and developed the responsive component and widgets.
- Created multiple **pipelines** in **azure DevOps** system.
- Collaborated to the project that was using an agile approach



Senior Flutter Developer Remote, Turkey | Jul 2021 - Sep 2022

<u>Rekab City</u> is a multi-module trip planner platform. You can easily plan your trip with public transport and get live updates about network interruptions.

- Contribute to an Open API generator package for flutter.
- Worked on **multimodule** (packages without dependencies) architecture.
- Struct Architecture based on MobX and Freezed in flutter.
- Worked with **Mapbox** as the main map of the app.
- Used **Hive** as main local database.
- Created a completely customized design system.
- · Worked with background services.



Senior Android, Flutter Developer

Iran, Gorgan | Jun 2019 - May 2020

Dropp Technologies is a company Which develops Mobile and Web applications. I have worked on several applications in Dropp and learned various concepts.

- Struct an architecture base on Bloc and Equatable.
- Use **Stripe methodology** for payments.
- Construct chat part with socket.io to increase the speed in comparison with Firebase.
- Work with animations and transitions in flutter.
- Experienced Google map package and Google services.

EDUCATIONAL

• Master of Software engineering Gorgan Azad University | 2017 - 2019

• Bachelor of Software engineering Gorgan Azad University | 2013 - 2017

VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCE



Community Staff

Persian Flutter, Jul 2021 - Present

PUBLISHED DOCUMENTS

- Flutter Navigator Middleware Part 1 RouteObserver
- Flutter Navigator Middleware Part 2 Middleware Service
- Persian Articles